SHIMES
We'll be right back.
The person I like is his older brother.
Then I guess I'll be extra generous this year.
I wonder if Chizu was able to give the present.
Thank you for everything.
Oh, please. The pleasure is all mine, really.
Hmm. All right. We'll come back to visit again for New Year's.
I guess she decided not to see me off this time.
Just like all young'uns, Chizu's probably just busy.
Ryu.
Hmm?
Hey, please tell Chizu I said to drop by. Anytime.
Hmm.
Yeah, sure thing. I'll tell her that.
It's so cold out.
It's hard to face him.
Hmm.
I don't know.
You're late.
What?
My brother left a message for you.
Said to drop by next time.
We left earlier today.
Well, no duh!
I already know that!
Are you...
Are you just coddling me?
Or are you trying to pick a fight?
Huh?
What?
Yeah.
So you didn't tell me about Toru
because you were trying to protect my feelings?
That wasn't my intention at all.
Actually,
I'm honestly relieved this finally happened.
Why?
Because now you can let yourself move on from your crush on my brother.
You're so stupid, Ryu!
Moron!
Baseball idiot!
What's baseball got to do with any of this?
Let's go.
Oh, my God!
Idiot!
to be honest i feel sort of useless right now jesus done so much for me but what can i do for her
i can't help but think if i were the kind of person kaze haya is
would i have been able to comfort her in this situation
morning sawako good morning
i wonder if chizu went to see ryu's brother after that though i kind of have an idea
do you think that she was able to congratulate him in that state
without showing signs of sadness congrats way to go man thanks chi
wearing jeans
yeah i get it just let it out it's okay
you know what i think chizu needs to express her feelings more often i feel so bad for her
not to mention what i said probably made her feel much worse about the whole situation
wait are you sure maybe it's not as bad as you think it is
and you're totally gonna find someone better
no it was pretty bad she even froze up for a second
but what did you say it couldn't have been that bad
please don't make me repeat it
i'd like to curl up and die now
no please don't do that i don't want you to die
to be honest i wouldn't care so much if it was someone that i was actually trying to hurt on purpose
uh what are you two doing
good question
what are the two of us doing right now
we're reflecting upon how it feels to be useless i guess
is any of this in relation to yoshida
i see
so that's what you two were all concerned about
wait a sec did you know too
about chizu's crush
whenever toru came back to visit
i always ran into her at ryu's house so
she is pretty obvious
so ayane felt the same as i did
she was worried about chizu
but also couldn't do anything
to be honest
i can't tell if she's playing cool
or if she's actually feeling so upset
that she's totally numb from the shock
that's the one thing that isn't obvious
that's right
chizu is acting cheerful
like her usual self
it makes it hard to tell what she's thinking
but i just know in my heart that she's not okay
i can tell
he's hurt
you see
we're no good
we're completely useless
are you okay
yoshida's gonna be fine
i'm sure of it
so relax
huh
yeah easy for you to say
typical man it's not your problem
go for it you're not that worried about it
that's not it
i said that because she's got you two
were you not listening to me earlier
i told you that we couldn't figure out a single thing to say to her
i was
but i don't think it's as big of a problem as you're assuming it is
i feel like if i were in yoshida's shoes right now
then it'd be nice to have people who worry about me like that
if you can't find the words to say there's no need to force it
i bet she'll really appreciate that you're even there for her at all
but keep in mind that she might be in a state where she doesn't know what to say either
what do you do in these situations
me
yeah joe just got rejected didn't he
i end up being pretty useless
oh
guess we should head to class now
yeah
what would kasehaya do
i've been wondering that since this started but
i see
even though i don't know what to say
kasehaya
i want to be of use to her somehow
yeah yeah
i hope i can be
thank you
kasehaya
can't believe i was cheered up by a wimp
huh
a wimp
now it's harder for me to tease him
i'm sure she'll be fine
she's got kuronuma
yano and
ryu as well
oh man
looks like sawako and yano chin aren't here yet
actually
i'm honestly relieved this
finally happened
oh
there you are
you're pretty late aren't you
g-good morning
hey
morning
so i ended up not seeing him the day before yesterday
sorry about that
you guys could have stayed longer
it's not that big a deal
i mean we see each other every day
sawako
come on
let's get seated
pin will be here any minute
that was close
i almost started tearing up
if jizu isn't crying right now
then i shouldn't be either
oh
oh hey
morning kazehaya
good morning
yoshida
if jizu starts venting
let's listen to everything she says
and let's let her mope around as much as she wants
yeah
i agree with you ayane
until then
i have to act as i normally would around jizu
like absolutely nothing's wrong
that may be
the only thing i'm able to do for her at the moment
hey what are you eating today kazehaya
cafeteria food
oh okay
what about you
rice boss
oh yeah
kazehaya
hurry up
coming
all right see you later
yeah
i'm gonna buy some bread to munch on
you want me to come with
nah it'll only take me a minute
if you're sure
be back in a jiffy
huh
come to think of it
those two haven't really talked today have they
oh no
you think something's wrong
i'm a little worried
i wonder
if ryu is going after her
i i have no idea
kind of concerning
give me an elizabeth
a half and half
the cheesy one
one with mayo
a bagel
melon pon
and a nutty one with dried fruits please
uh yeah sure
man i love bread
cheese it
my bread
my bad
but you won't even bother looking at me so
listen
to what
i think i've listened to enough of your crap
or did you come to apologize
that's not why i'm here
not apologizing for what i said
tell me
is that how you saw me this entire time
that i've always liked toru
even though you knew
i didn't stand a chance with him
and you figured
i should just hurry
and be heartbroken
well i didn't start liking him to end up with a broken heart
who would even do that to themselves
as for yesterday
just so you know
the reason i came over wasn't to see him
what's going on
are they fighting
but you
that's where you were like
you're late shizuru
you should know by now
if it was possible
then he would have been there
to see toru before he left
but
i couldn't do it
i couldn't
so when i came with your present
i already figured
he'd be long gone by then
when i got there
you had to go ahead
and be a damn idiot
didn't you
ow
your bread
chizuru
i don't need it
you can have it
and don't talk to me for a while
how am i supposed to eat all this by myself
well i didn't start liking him to end up with a broken heart
who would even do that to themselves
you should at least let me thank you
chizu
why are
you here
well
we just
got a little worried
did you guys
happen to see all of that
yeah
that's embarrassing
ryu and i got into a little fight last night
so
i
can't hold back anymore
hey
i'm sorry
i'm really so sorry
i was wondering why you had that weird frown on your face
take this and clean up
thank you
oh
jizu
hey what's wrong
you okay
i'm pissed
ryu really pisses me off
yesterday i went over to his house so that i could give him his present
i got the courage to go
and it was all just an awkward mess
he was relieved that i found out
and he said i could give up now
can you believe it
he actually thought i never stood a chance at hell
that stupid idiot
that stupid idiot is way too honest
jizu
he saw me as a poor little girl all this time
how could he
he's so mad
he's such a jerk
but
if i'm being real
now i'm mostly just pissed off at myself
i took this all out on him
and the way i used his present
i was excited to hand it over
it was gonna be special
but i threw it at him
i hate this
toru's marriage
it hasn't even fully hit me yet
but i'm already
taking out my anger on ryu
she's moping
she's actually doing it
i'm so happy
yeah
you're happy
what are you waiting for
keep going jizu
i know there's more
so complain away
if you don't take all your anger out
when's the next time you're gonna get the chance
i mean considering what he did
you went easy on him
what he did was totally messed up
yeah
it's totally true
so you
would have done the same
heck yeah
i'd have done worse
the thing with the present
it wouldn't have happened
because i would have tossed it
yeah
you mean it
chizu
you were in the right there
hmm
yanochi
sawaka
there there
vent all you want
you know what
it's so messed up
when i
went over to see for you
the first thing he says to me is
you're late
i shouldn't have let him have my bread
i'm so hungry
in the end
i wasn't able to find a single word to say to chizu to bring her comfort
however
while we were making our way home that day
she said
hey
yeah what's up
sawako's crying made me cry
and i started to feel better
oh hey
i have an idea
let's get all you can eat cake
sure
come on hurry up yanochin
okay okay okay
you know
i eat way too many sweets when i'm with you
yes
hello
so uh
i've got a lot of bread here
you want some
huh
it's just some bread that chizuru left for me
it's just some bread that you got
really
oh
it's just some breadboil
in
Ah, just show one for me.
You